<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to St. Joseph’s Roman Catholic High School on St. Joseph’s Roman Catholic High School</title>
    <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to St. Joseph’s Roman Catholic High School on St. Joseph’s Roman Catholic High School</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>St Joseph’s RC High School Sefton Lane, Horwich, Bolton, BL6 6HW
Telephone – 01204 697456
Email – office@st-josephs.bolton.sch.uk
How to Find Us </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Pattern</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/holiday-pattern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/holiday-pattern/</guid>
      <description>A copy of our Holiday Pattern for the academic year 2021-2022 and 2022-3 can be downloaded as a PDF document below:
Holiday Dates 2022 2023
Holiday Dates 2023 2024
Holiday Dates 2024 2025
Use the link below to see a summary of our events in the 2022/2023 academic year. A summary is also listed at the bottom of the page: Parents/Carers Dates for Diary 2022-2023
*All events are subject to change/become virtual events depending on government guidelines</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information About JOEYS RCHS</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/information/</guid>
      <description>Welcome from the Headteacher St Joseph&amp;rsquo;s is a Catholic school that prides itself on high standards, outstanding students, and exceptional staff. Their Catholic mission and ethos are central to all they do, and they are committed to caring for each individual student. The school has a vibrant community and welcomes anyone considering joining as a student, parent, or staff member.
The school is proud of its recent improvements, and the leadership team is ambitious to become the best school possible for their students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Vacancies</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/job-vacancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/job-vacancies/</guid>
      <description>St. Joseph’s employ approximately 110 teaching and support staff and has approximately 958 students enrolled. The school provides education for students from age 11 to 16 and we are based within the Roman Catholic Diocese of Salford.
St. Joseph’s actively promotes policies, procedures and practices to safeguard the welfare of children and our staff. The school is committed to equality and diversity in all aspects of employment.
For any queries related to job vacancies, please email our Personal Assistant to the Headteacher, Mr T McCabe at recruitment@st-josephs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offsted Parent View</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/offsted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/offsted/</guid>
      <description> &lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Community at St Joseph&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/our-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/our-community/</guid>
      <description>Alumni New and exciting adventure: If you’re a former student of St Joseph’s RC High School, we want to hear from you!
Lifelong friendships and treasured memories are formed at St Joseph’s. Skills and abilities are mastered to aid students in the future.
If you think you can help transform our students confidence, motivation, skills and inspire a future generation we want to hear from you…
St Joseph’s Careers have partnered up with St Joseph’s Facebook to create an amazing opportunity for former students to keep in touch with us, to offer inspiration to our current students, offer specialised knowledge and stay connected with other former students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our School</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>St. Joseph’s is an 11-16 voluntary aided co-educational Roman Catholic Secondary School under the trusteeship of The Diocese of Salford. We are maintained by the Bolton Local Authority and have 860 students enrolled. St. Joseph’s was established as a secondary school on 5th November 1963.
The school has a long-standing reputation for high academic achievement, being an orderly, caring and welcoming community and provision for an extensive range of extra-curricular and out of hours activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ParentPay – cashless system of payment</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/parentpay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/parentpay/</guid>
      <description>ParentPay is a cashless system for schools, ensuring safety and peace of mind. Top up meals and pay for activities using accepted payment methods, and daily balance updates reflect your child&amp;rsquo;s meal choices. Check out the flyer and visit the ParentPay website by clicking here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Prospectus</title>
      <link>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/school-prospectus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joeys-rchs.pages.dev/posts/school-prospectus/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
